eveningflavors.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Online Bangalore Restaurants, Pubs, Parties Guide from eveningflavors.com

**For Booking and Info Call :** **080-40894999**

**Plan and book your dining and partying venue**

  *  
  * Restaurants Restaurant By Area | Restaurant By Cuisine | Speciality Restaurants |  Five Star | 
  * Buffet Lunch Buffet | Dinner Buffet | Breakfast Buffet | Midnight Buffet | Brunch | 
  *  Offers
  * Pubs & Bars
  * Parties | DJ Parties | Food Festival | Karaoke Night | Live Performance | 
  * Plan a party | Corporate Parties | Special Occasion Parties | Wedding Parties | Get Together Parties | Casual Outing | 
  * Resorts | Bannerghatta Road | Tumkur Road | Mysore Road | Kanakapura Road | Hosur Road | 

EveningFlavors.com  takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

What this Privacy Policy Covers   

  * This Privacy Policy covers Eveningflavors.com treatment of personally identifiable information that Eveningflavors.com collects when you are on our site, and when you use our services. This policy also covers Eveningflavors.com treatment of any personally identifiable information that our business partners share with our company.

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Eveningflavors.com does not own or control or to people that Eveningflavors.com does not employ or manage. 

Information Collection and Use   

  * Eveningflavors.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Eveningflavors.com account, when you use certain Eveningflavors.com products or services, when you visit Eveningflavors.com pages. Eveningflavors.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

  * When you register with Eveningflavors.com, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Eveningflavors.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

  * Eveningflavors.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Eveningflavors.com cookie information and the page you requested.

  * In addition, when you use Eveningflavors.com's services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return and Eveningflavors.com will not be responsible for the use or misuse of such information.

  * Eveningflavors.com uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services promoted by Eveningflavors.com or other companies, and to contact you about specials and new products. Eveningflavors.com is not responsible for the accuracy, completeness, veracity and reliability of any advertising and content, products and services which may be accessed or advertised to you and Eveningflavors.com will not be liable for any loss or damage arising out of the same.

Information Sharing and Disclosure   

  * Eveningflavors.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

  * Eveningflavors.com will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
    * We have your consent to share the information;

    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 

    * We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues. (Unless we tell you differently, these partners have no independent right to use this information except to respond to your comments or to resolve the service issues.);

    * We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;

    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or

    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Eveningflavors.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

Cookies  

  * Eveningflavors.com may set and access Eveningflavors.com cookies on your computer and you may not be able to disable these cookies. Eveningflavors.com ensures that all information collected and accessed by Eveningflavors.com through the access of these cookies will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

  * Eveningflavors.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Eveningflavors.com 's cookies. 

  * Eveningflavors.com uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with Eveningflavors.com products and services. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  

  * Eveningflavors.com gives you the ability to edit your Eveningflavors.com Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Eveningflavors.com to contact you about specials and new products. Eveningflavors.com is not responsible and will not be liable for the accuracy, completeness, veracity and reliability of any information including any customized information which may be accessed by or provided to you, which could vary depending on your Eveningflavors.com Account Information and preferences including your browser preferences. 

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Eveningflavors.com does not own or control or to people that Eveningflavors.com does not employ or manage.

Security  

  * Your Eveningflavors.com account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 

  * In certain areas Eveningflavors.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

Changes to this Privacy Policy  

  * Eveningflavors.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

Questions or Suggestions  

  * If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form.

© 2009-14 Evening Flavors. All rights reserved.
